<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Guillaume&#39;s graphics blog</title>
    <link>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Guillaume&#39;s graphics blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gboisse.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Road to Revision 2023</title>
      <link>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/revision-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/revision-2023/</guid>
      <description>Back in 2021, I got in touch with Made in the hope that we could join our efforts in creating a PC demo for Revision. Made has been making demos for years and had recently won two Revision parties in that category, an impressive feat. So I sent him a couple of renders I made with my personal engine hoping that&amp;rsquo;d get him excited enough&amp;hellip;
He accepted pretty much instantly, so we started talking about various creative ideas and quickly settled on a concept that he had on the backburner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual node graph with ImGui</title>
      <link>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/node-graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/node-graph/</guid>
      <description>I wanted my first post on this blog to be about the node graph system that I created for my personal graphics engine named &amp;ldquo;RogueEngine&amp;rdquo;. I may talk about the engine itself in another post but for now I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on its UI.
As a teaser, here&amp;rsquo;s a screenshot of the tool running our Revision 2023 demo:
Intro sequence from Reality Check.
A bit of background I started thinking about this project back in 2019 with the aim of releasing some PC demo productions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gboisse.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This will (hopefully) be a place for me to share about my personal experiments in the world of real-time graphics and demomaking, stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
